Nikita Borisenko

Contact Details:

690021, Bryanskaya 18, Vladivostok, Russia ceaselessclosure@mail.ru

Tel, What's App: +7 (953) 208-40-08

Telegram: @whitenullzero

Summary:

Highly motivated experienced Developer. Most of the time I've been developing frontends. Now I am more interested in software/backend development, preferably in Rust. Completely focused until the problem is solved. Accustomed to taking greater responsibility for decisions as I was IE and LLC founder and feel stable in a stressful environment. Honestly, I am constantly monitoring market trends and new technologies, ceaselessly developing.

Skills:

Frontend (TypeScript) - Senior Backend (Rust / Python) - Middle Data Analyst: (R / Python) - Middle Software Developer (Rust, Python) -Middle

DevOps - Middle

Languages:

Russian (native) English (C1)

Education:

Maritime State University, Vladivostok 2018-2022, B.A.

Technology of transport processes

Maritime State University, Vladivostok 2018-2020, B.A.

English Interpreter

Vladivostok State University, Vladivostok 2022 - now , M.A.

Applied computer science: Artificial intelligence and machine learning in management and decision-making

Work Experience:

Freelance, fullstack (2018-2021) CIS, Full remote. Fullstack projects with ReactJS+NodeJS+PostgreSQL, PHP.

IE, Vladivostok (2021 – 2022) *Vladivostok, CEO, Founder.*Offline + E-shop with with its self-written CRM (NextJS, NodeJS).

LLC Neurone-IT, (2022-2024) *Vladivostok, CEO, Founder.* Web development, Software development, promotion, design.

Vladivostok State University, (2023 - now) *Vladivostok, Teacher.* Classes: HTML/CSS, OOP TypeScript, NodeJS, ReactJS+ReduxTK.

Freelance, (2023 - now) Full-remote, development and full support of 3 CIS projects

1. Payment Gateway.

Frontend: NextJS, Zustand, Typescript, SASS.

Backend: Python (Nodriver webdriver, bs4, tornado), NodeJS (bun,

elysiais, cors, prisma, postgresgl),

CI/CD/DEV: GitLab, Docker, NGINX, VNC, bash)

2. senatcars.ru

Parser: Python, bs4, selenium, multiprocessing.

Backend: Rust (tokio, axum, tower http)

Microservice: NodeJS+Mongodb (save parsed cars)

Microservice: Rust (tokio, sqlx) + PostgreSQL (compare and serve

cars)

Microservice: Rust (reqwest, sqlx) (leads and users) **CI/CD/DEV**: Git:Lab, Docker, NGINX, VNC, bash)

3. CABAN (Car Auction Buffer Access Network) local tools for analysis, managing leads, users, db and parsing 5m cars from Korean and Japan auctions per day.

Parsers & scrappers: tokio, scraper, http(reqwest, ureq, hyper) with threading.

Backend: actix-web, tokio (websocket rest-api with broadcasting) **Backend**: NodeJS + bun, Prisma, Typescript (manage leads and

users)

Data: Postgresql, redis.

Frontend: NextJS, Zustand, Typescript

CI/CD/DEV: GitLab, Docker, NGINX, VNC, bash, K8S

Monitors: Grafana + Prometheus

OCR (Python): multilayer perceptrons, scikit, tesseract,

keras(Sequential) + opencv

Data Analytics & Visualisations (R):

- Tests: (shapiro, ks, lillie, cvm, pearson, chisq, fisher, mantelhaen, grubbs, kruskal, wilcox, ADF, ACF)
 - Correlation: (spearman, kendall),
 - Visual: (histograms, barplots, tables, plots, boxplots, ggplots)